Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
EPISODE 8
LIM HYEON-JUN
GOOD ACTOR LIM HYEON-JUN
OFFICIAL FAN PAGE
VIEW RECENT POSTS
I'M CURRENTLY IDOLIZING
LIM HYEON-JUN
HE RADIATES AN AMAZING AURA WITH
HIS CHISELED GOOD LOOKS AND VIBE
ON TOP OF HIS STUNNING
GOOD LOOKS, HE EXUDES CLASS
SOULISHERE
POSTED BY:
"EXCITEMENT
AND DOPAMINE OVERLOAD,
VIEWERS HOOKED ON THE KISS"
SPORTS EUNSEONG
WI JEONG-SIN
[SPECIAL REPORT] SERIA,
A CITY IN RUINS, STILL CRIES OUT
GOOD ACTOR LIM HYEON-JUN
1 REPLY TO YOUR POST
LIM HYEON-JUN - HELLO,
THIS IS ACTOR LIM HYEON-JUN.
"EXCITEMENT
AND DOPAMINE OVERLOAD,
VIEWERS HOOKED ON THE KISS"
HAESONG FUNERAL HALL
FUNERAL HALL
LIM HYEON-JUN & GWON SE-NA
PAY THEIR RESPECTS
TO THE LATE LEE GI-CHUN
PSYCHIATRIST - YOU EUN-KYOUNG
IF YOU MAKE A WISH UPON
A FULL MOON,
YOUR WISH WILL COME TRUE
YOU MUST BE
REALLY BUSY THESE DAYS
SPORTS EUNSEONG
IT'S SUPPOSED TO RAIN TODAY
GOOD DETECTIVE KANG PIL-GU 5
AUDITION WAITING AREA
CANDIDATE 24, LIM SEON-U
HAMCHORONG
SEON-U
MY BIG BRO
I WAS ON MY WAY TO WORK
AND SAW THESE GORGEOUS FLOWERS!
INVITATION
MELOMASTER
SOULISHERE SENT YOU A MESSAGE.
BEST FIRST DATE SPOTS
BEST DATE SPOTS IN SEOUL
LOVE LOCKS & OBSERVATION DECK
ESPECIALLY BEAUTIFUL
AT SUNSET AND AFTER DARK
DELETE APP
APPOINTMENT BOOKED
AGENCIES MERGE: GWON SE-NA
& LIM HYEON-JUN UNDER ONE ROOF!
EUNSEONG
CHAIRMAN LEE DAE-HO
HWANG JI-SUN
SPORTS EUNSEONG
AN APPOINTMENT HAS BEEN BOOKED.
SOULISHERE (NAMSAN SEOUL TOWER
LOVE LOCKS) TODAY, 8 P.M.
NEW RECORDING 1
SPECIAL THANKS TO OH YEON-SEO
FOR HER APPEARANCE